Chandler, Alfred D., 1918-2007. Papers, 1941-2004: A Finding Aid
Alfred D. Chandler papers, 1940-2007
- Series II. Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Johns Hopkins University, 1949-1978
  - Subseries N. Johns Hopkins University External Activities: Memberships, 1956-1972
    - Business History Review, 1957 (Box 66, f. 5)
    - Business History Review, 1958-1959 (Box 66, f. 6)
    - Business History Review, 1960-1961 (Box 66, f. 7)
    - Business History Review, 1962-1969 (Box 66, f. 8)
    - Economic Development: Committee for, 1966-1967 (Box 66, f. 9)
    - Economic Development: Committee for, 1970-1971 (Box 66, f. 10)
    - Economic History Association, 1966-1968 (Box 66, f. 11)
    - Economic History Association, 1970-1971 (Box 66, f. 12)
    - Economic History Association: Council on Research in Economic History, 1968-1969 (Box 66, f. 13)
    - Economic History Association: Journal of Economic History, 1966-1971 (Box 66, f. 14)
    - Eleutherian Mills-Hagley Foundation Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 66, f. 15-16)
    - Harcourt Brace and World: Forces in American Economic History Series, Jan. - June 1963 (Box 66, f. 17)
    - Harcourt Brace and World:: Forces in American Economic History Series, July - Dec. 1963 (Box 66, f. 18)
    - Harcourt Brace and World:: Forces in American Economic History Series, Jan. - June 1964 (Box 66, f. 19)
    - Harcourt Brace and World:: Forces in American Economic History Series, July - Dec. 1964 (Box 66, f. 20)
    - Harcourt Brace and World:: Forces in American Economic History Series, Jan. - May 1965 (Box 67, f. 1)
    - Harcourt Brace and World:: Forces in American Economic History Series, June - Dec. 1965 (Box 67, f. 2)
    - Harcourt Brace and World:: Forces in American Economic History Series, 1966-1967 (Box 67, f. 3)
    - MIT Visiting Committee, 1967 (Box 67, f. 4)
    - MIT Visiting Committee, 1968 (Box 67, f. 5)
    - MIT Visiting Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 67, f. 6)
    - MIT Visiting Committee: Printed Material, 1969-1970 (Box 67, f. 7)
    - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development: Correspondence, etc., 1970 (Box 67, f. 8)
    - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development: Correspondence, etc., 1971 (Box 67, f. 9)
    - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development, Oct. 16-17, 1970 (Box 67, f. 10)
    - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development, Dec. 11-12, 1970 (Box 67, f. 11)
    - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development, Feb. 19-20, 1971 (Box 67, f. 12)
    - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development, May 21-22, 1971 (Box 67, f. 13)
    - National Advisory Council on Education Professions Development: "Windows to the Bureaucracy", 1972 (Box 67, f. 14)
    - Organization of American Historians, 1969 (Box 67, f. 15)
    - Organization of American Historians, 1970 (Box 67, f. 16)
    - Organization of American Historians, 1971 (Box 68, f. 1)
    - Social Science Research Council: Grants-in-Aid Committee, 1959-1964 (Box 68, f. 2-5)
- Series III. Harvard Business School (HBS), Active Tenure, 1968-1991
  This series consists of records created and collected by Alfred Chandler during his active tenure at HBS as Isidor Straus Professor of Business History (1970–1989) and during his transition to Professor Emeritus (1989-1991). This series includes correspondence and subject files, research and writings (including research related to The Visible Hand and Scale and Scope), and materials related to teaching, attending conferences, and professional memberships.
  The series occasionally includes records created at an earlier or later period because they were inter-filed by Chandler.
  - Subseries A. HBS Correspondence and Subject Files, Active Tenure, 1968-1988
    The bulk of the material in this subseries falls between 1970 and 1987. Some correspondence is dated well before Alfred Chandler's tenure at HBS. These early letters include correspondence with Arthur Cole, economic historian and Harvard Business School librarian, from 1962, which has been retained here to preserve the original order. This subseries consists of letters to Chandler and copies of letters from him. Accompanying the correspondence are photocopied articles, reprints, and manuscripts. The topics covered in this series include appraisal of his work by others (often including annotated manuscripts), exchanges of views and information on aspects of business history, requests for reviews, invitations to speak, permissions, and travel arrangements.
    Correspondence relating to Alfred Chandler's appointment to the Isidor Straus Chair at HBS and his reports on his research activities and plans to the Division of Research and Faculty Development and to the Dean of Harvard Business School have been separated and placed in the fifty-year restricted Administration and Program records.
    - A: Aaron-Auton, 1971-1986 (Box 69, f. 1)
    - Abernathy, Bill, 1976-1984 (Box 69, f. 2)
    - Abrams, Richard M., 1973 (Box 69, f. 3)
    - Academia Italiana di Economica Aziendale, 1981-1985 (Box 69, f. 4)
    - Academy of Management, The, 1972-1973 (Box 69, f. 5)
    - Addresses, 1979-1980 (Box 69, f. 6)
    - Agarwala, P.N., 1985 (Box 69, f. 7)
    - Aitken, Hugh, 1970-1985 (Box 69, f. 8)
    - Akin, Edward N., 1982 (Box 69, f. 9)
    - Alcan Aluminum Limited, Montreal, 1980 (Box 69, f. 10)
    - Alchon, Guy, 1982 (Box 69, f. 11)
    - Alford, Bernard, 1974-1985 (Box 69, f. 12)
    - Alford, Richard, 1980 (Box 69, f. 13)
    - All Souls College, Oxford, 1973-1979 (Box 69, f. 14-15)
    - Altman, Elizabeth, 1981 (Box 69, f. 16)
    - Amatori, Franco, 1977-1987 (Box 69, f. 17)
    - Ambrose, Stephen E., 1970-1987 (Box 69, f. 18-19)
    - American Antiquarian Society, 1978-1983 (Box 69, f. 20)
    - American Historical Association, 1971-1985 (Box 69, f. 21)
    - American Jewish History, 1983 (Box 69, f. 22)
    - American Journal of Sociology, 1981 (Box 69, f. 23)
    - American Trust for the British Library, 1980-1981 (Box 69, f. 24)
    - Amick, Benjamin C., 1987 (Box 69, f. 25)
    - Amory, Robert, III, 1981 (Box 69, f. 26)
    - Anderson, Alan, undated (Box 69, f. 27)
    - Anderson, Douglas D., 1985 (Box 69, f. 28)
    - Andreano, Ralph L., 1970-1971 (Box 69, f. 29)
    - Andrews, Kenneth, 1980-1982 (Box 69, f. 30)
    - Antonelli, Christiano, 1983-1987 (Box 69, f. 31)
    - Arbetslivscentrum: Stockholm, Sweden, 1987 (Box 69, f. 32)
    - Archives, 1984 (Box 69, f. 33)
    - Ariel Editorial: Barcelona, Spain, 1983-1987 (Box 69, f. 34)
    - Aries, Roberts, 1984 (Box 69, f. 35)
    - Arno Press, 1979-1983 (Box 70, f. 1-3)
    - Arnold, Wright H., 1982 (Box 70, f. 4)
    - Arthur, Henry B., 1982-1983 (Box 70, f. 5)
    - Associated University Presses, 1980 (Box 70, f. 6)
    - Associazione di storia e studi sull’impresa, 1983 (Box 70, f. 7)
    - Atack, Jeremy, 1984-1987 (Box 70, f. 8)
    - AT&T, 1979-1986 (Box 70, f. 9)
    - Athos, Anthony G., 1981 (Box 70, f. 10)
    - Austin, Barbara, 1983 (Box 70, f. 11)
    - The Authors’ Guild, 1972-1973 (Box 70, f. 12)
    - Avco Corporation, 1983 (Box 70, f. 13)
    - Averitt, Robert T., 1974-1981 (Box 70, f. 14)
    - B: Bailyn-Bell, 1970-1986 (Box 70, f. 15)
    - B: Bemis-Bogus, 1972-1986 (Box 70, f. 16)
    - B: Bontje-Byron, 1973-1987 (Box 70, f. 17)
    - Babson College, 1981-1982 (Box 70, f. 18)
    - Ball, George, 1980 (Box 70, f. 19)
    - Balle, Catherine, 1982-1986 (Box 70, f. 20)
    - Ballen, Ken, 1976 (Box 70, f. 21)
    - Bamford, P.W., 1984 (Box 70, f. 22)
    - Bancroft Award, Columbia University, 1978 (Box 70, f. 23)
    - Baritz, Loren, 1972 (Box 70, f. 24)
    - Barker, Theodore, 1975-1987 (Box 70, f. 25)
    - Barnard, John, 1984 (Box 70, f. 26)
    - Barrett, Jane, 1975 (Box 70, f. 27)
    - Bartley, Numan V., 1974 (Box 70, f. 28)
    - Basic Books, Inc., 1973-1983 (Box 70, f. 29)
    - Basil Blackwell Publishers, 1982-1983 (Box 70, f. 30)
    - Bateman, Fred, 1973-1977 (Box 70, f. 31)
    - Battis, Robert A., 1977 (Box 70, f. 32)
    - Baudet, Henri, 1975 (Box 70, f. 33)
    - Bauer, Ray, 1976 (Box 70, f. 34)
    - Baughman, James P., 1969-1981 (Box 70, f. 35)
    - Beach, Alfred, undated (Box 70, f. 36)
    - Beach, William W., 1972 (Box 70, f. 37)
    - Bean, L.L., 1984 (Box 70, f. 38)
    - Beard, Miriam/Gummere, Richard, 1982-1983 (Box 70, f. 39)
    - Bartoshevsky, Florence, 1982-1983 (Box 70, f. 40)
    - Becker, William H., 1972-1987 (Box 70, f. 41-42)
    - Bendana, Alejandro, 1974-1976 (Box 70, f. 43)
    - Beninger, James, 1984-1987 (Box 70, f. 44)
    - Benjamin, Saul, 1984 (Box 71, f. 1)
    - Benson, Richard, 1976-1980 (Box 71, f. 2)
    - Berg, Norm, 1977-1983 (Box 71, f. 3)
    - Berger, Ronald M., 1978-1984 (Box 71, f. 4)
    - Bernstein, Irving, 1976 (Box 71, f. 5)
    - Berry, William L., 1977 (Box 71, f. 6)
    - Bethlehem Steel Corp., 1983 (Box 71, f. 7)
    - Bethlem, Agicola de Souza, 1981-1984 (Box 71, f. 8)
    - Betsky, Seymour, 1981-1984 (Box 71, f. 9)
    - Bhargava, Narottam, 1973 (Box 71, f. 10)
    - Biographical Encyclopedia of American Businessmen, 1985-1987 (Box 71, f. 11)
    - Bishop, Charles W., 1973 (Box 71, f. 12)
    - Blackford, Mansel, 1977-1984 (Box 71, f. 13)
    - Blondheim, Menachem, 1986 (Box 71, f. 14)
    - Blouin, Francis X., Jr., 1982-1984 (Box 71, f. 15)
    - Blum, Mitchell, 1973-1975 (Box 71, f. 16)
    - Blum, John M., 1971-1983 (Box 71, f. 17)
    - Bobbs-Merrill Company, 1974-1978 (Box 71, f. 18)
    - Boisot, Max (See also: Kuhn, Sarah file), 1981 (Box 71, f. 19)
    - Bolton, John E., 1973 (Box 71, f. 20)
    - Book Reviews, 1973-1979 (Box 71, f. 21)
    - Borneman, Alfred H., 1973 (Box 71, f. 22)
    - Bornkamp, A., 1975 (Box 71, f. 23)
    - Bos, Dieter, 1982-1986 (Box 71, f. 24)
    - Boston 200, 1973-1974 (Box 71, f. 25)
    - Boswell, Jonathan S., 1976-1987 (Box 71, f. 26-28)
    - Both, Richard, 1972 (Box 71, f. 29)
    - Bovykin, V.I., 1979 (Box 71, f. 30)
    - Bradley, Joseph, 1977 (Box 71, f. 31)
    - Bradley University, 1979 (Box 71, f. 32)
    - Braendel, Doris B., 1975 (Box 71, f. 33)
    - Braentigam, Ronald R., 1983 (Box 71, f. 34)
    - Bragaw, Louis K. (Coast Guard Academy), 1976-1979 (Box 71, f. 35)
    - Brandeis University, 1980-1984 (Box 71, f. 36)
    - Breslin, Robert W., 1971 (Box 71, f. 37)
    - Broehl, Wayne G., Jr., 1978-1984 (Box 71, f. 38)
    - Brogan, Martha L., 1983 (Box 71, f. 39)
    - Bronk, Detlev W., 1974 (Box 71, f. 40)
    - Brophy, Sean, 1983-1985 (Box 71, f. 41)
    - Brouillard Communications, 1981-1982 (Box 71, f. 42)
    - Brown, Jonathan, 1981-1983 (Box 71, f. 43)
    - Bruchey, Stuart, 1970-1987 (Box 71, f. 44-45)
    - Brustio, Cesare, 1982-1985 (Box 71, f. 46)
    - Bryant, Douglas W., 1979 (Box 71, f. 47)
    - Bryant, Lynwood, 1972-1977 (Box 71, f. 48)
    - Bunting, David, 1980-1983 (Box 72, f. 1)
    - Burner, David, 1978-1979 (Box 72, f. 2)
    - Burns, Malcolm, 1982 (Box 72, f. 3)
    - Busch, E. Walter, 1981 (Box 72, f. 4)
    - Business and Archives Council, 1974-1975 (Box 72, f. 5)
    - Business and Economic History, 1982 (Box 72, f. 6)
    - Business and Public Policy, 1981 (Box 72, f. 7)
    - Buss, Dietrich, 1977 (Box 72, f. 8)
    - Buzzell, Robert, 1974 (Box 72, f. 9)
    - Byrt, W.J., 1975-1976 (Box 72, f. 10)
    - C: Cable-Chavenon, 1971-1987 (Box 72, f. 11)
    - C: Checkland-Consagra, 1971-1987 (Box 72, f. 12)
    - C: Cooling-Czarniawska, 1972-1986 (Box 72, f. 13)
    - Cabot Corporation, 1979 (Box 72, f. 14)
    - Calvin, Melvin, 1980 (Box 72, f. 15)
    - Cambridge Scientific Club, 1983-1984 (Box 72, f. 16)
    - Cambridge University Press, 1971-1987 (Box 72, f. 17)
    - Cameron, Rondo, 1973-1983 (Box 72, f. 18)
    - Canada, Council, The, 1978 (Box 72, f. 19)
    - Caron, Francois, 1980-1985 (Box 72, f. 20)
    - Carosso, Vincent P, 1971-1983 (Box 72, f. 21)
    - Case, Everett, 1979-1985 (Box 72, f. 22)
    - Catudal, Honore, Jr., 1972 (Box 72, f. 23)
    - Caves, Richard E., 1978-1986 (Box 72, f. 24)
    - Center for Advanced Study in Behavioral Sciences, 1977 (Box 72, f. 25)
    - Center for the History of Chemistry, 1984-1987 (Box 72, f. 26)
    - Chakravarthy, Bala, 1978-1986 (Box 72, f. 27-28)
    - Chandler, Alfred D.: Comments on Industry, 1977-1982 (Box 72, f. 29)
    - Chandler, Alfred D.: Comments on Industry, 1983 (Box 73, f. 1)
    - Chandler, Alfred D.: Personal Correspondence, 1972-1987 (Box 73, f. 2)
    - Chandler, Alfred D.: 60th Birthday, 1978 (Box 73, f. 3)
    - Chandler, Tertius, 1971-1987 (Box 73, f. 4)
    - Channon, Derek, 1972-1984 (Box 73, f. 5)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, N.A., 1981-1984 (Box 73, f. 6)
    - Cheape, Charles, 1972-1987 (Box 73, f. 7)
    - Chicago, University of, Press, 1973-1984 (Box 73, f. 8)
    - Chief Executive’s Handbook, 1974-1976 (Box 73, f. 9)
    - Child, John, 1981 (Box 73, f. 10)
    - Citycorp: Eli Ginzberg, 1979-1980 (Box 73, f. 11-13)
    - Clark, John G., 1975-1987 (Box 73, f. 14)
    - Clippings, 1981 (Box 73, f. 15)
    - Clifton, James A., 1975-1977 (Box 73, f. 16)
    - Cochran, Alexander S., 1972-1975 (Box 73, f. 17)
    - Cochran, Thomas C., 1962-1980 (Box 73, f. 18)
    - Cohen, Henry, 1972-1980 (Box 73, f. 19)
    - Cole, Arthur, 1962-1977 (Box 73, f. 20)
    - Cole, Arthur-Entrepreneurship, the Business System..., 1972 (Box 73, f. 21)
    - Cole, A./Cochran, T.: Correspondence, 1962-1977 (Box 73, f. 22)
    - Coleman, Donald, 1977-1984 (Box 73, f. 23)
    - Coleman, William, 1972-1978 (Box 73, f. 24)
    - Collected Essays (Japanese edition), 1986 (Box 73, f. 25)
    - Columbia University Press, 1982-1987 (Box 74, f. 1)
    - Coming of Managerial Capitalism ... (Chandler/Tedlow), 1984-1987 (Box 74, f. 2)
    - Conference Board, 1977-1986 (Box 74, f. 3)
    - Continental Oil Company, 1976 (Box 74, f. 4)
    - Corporate Director Journal, 1980 (Box 74, f. 5)
    - Cost of Living Council, 1972-1974 (Box 74, f. 6)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 74, f. 7)
    - Crowe, Violette, 1979 (Box 74, f. 8)
    - Crown Program, Brandeis University, 1979-1982 (Box 74, f. 9)
    - Cuff, Robert D., 1972-1983 (Box 74, f. 10)
    - Cunningham, James Patrick, 1983 (Box 74, f. 11)
    - Cusamano, Michael, 1984 (Box 74, f. 12)
    - D: Dahlsten-Dyer, 1972-1987 (Box 74, f. 13-14)
    - Daedalus, 1974-1985 (Box 74, f. 15)
    - Daems, Herman, 1971-1986 (Box 74, f. 16)
    - Daems, Herman: Writings, 1976-1985 (Box 75, f. 1)
    - David, Paul A., 1973-1974 (Box 75, f. 2)
    - Davies, Robert B., 1975-1977 (Box 75, f. 3)
    - Davis, Donald, 1974-1979 (Box 75, f. 4)
    - Davis, Stanley, 1972-1987 (Box 75, f. 5)
    - de Jouvenel, Bertrand, 1972-1975 (Box 75, f. 6)
    - Deere and Company, undated (Box 75, f. 7)
    - Dictionary of American Economic History, 1974-1976 (Box 75, f. 8)
    - Didrichsen, Jon C., 1977 (Box 75, f. 9)
    - Dilts, James D., 1982-1983 (Box 75, f. 10)
    - Dioguardi, Gianfranco, 1975-1987 (Box 75, f. 11-13)
    - Diebold Group, The, 1980-1983 (Box 75, f. 14)
    - Doerflinger, Thomas M., 1982-1986 (Box 75, f. 15)
    - Donald, David Herbert, 1972-1974 (Box 75, f. 16)
    - Donaldson, Lex, 1983-1987 (Box 75, f. 17-18)
    - Douglas, Withers, JKI, 1984 (Box 75, f. 19)
    - Downs, Jacques M., 1974-1979 (Box 75, f. 20)
    - Ducey, John, 1986 (Box 75, f. 21)
    - Dunlavy, Colleen, 1981-1986 (Box 76, f. 1)
    - Dupree, A. Hunter, 1978 (Box 76, f. 2)
    - du Pont, P.S., 1982-1983 (Box 76, f. 3)
    - E: Ealing-Explorations.., 1970-1987 (Box 76, f. 4)
    - Economic History Review, 1979-1980 (Box 76, f. 5)
    - Eichner, Alfred S., 1975-1982 (Box 76, f. 6-8)
    - Eisenhower Papers, 1970-1983 (Box 76, f. 9)
    - Elbaum, Bernard, 1987 (Box 76, f. 10)
    - Eliot House (Harvard College), 1972-1982 (Box 76, f. 11)
    - Elliott, Ord, undated (Box 76, f. 12)
    - Encyclopedia of American Economic History, 1979 (Box 76, f. 13)
    - Engerman, Stanley L., 1972-1978 (Box 76, f. 14)
    - England Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 76, f. 15)
    - Engelbourg, Saul, 1973-1982 (Box 76, f. 16)
    - Epp, Ernest, 1971-1978 (Box 76, f. 17)
    - Epstein, Edwin M., 1973-1984 (Box 76, f. 18-19)
    - European Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 76, f. 20-24)
    - European Institute for Advanced Studies in Management, 1972-1979 (Box 76, f. 25-26)
    - F: Fabris-Foreman, 1970-1986 (Box 76, f. 27)
    - F: Foote-Freehling, 1971-1987 (Box 76, f. 28)
    - Fairbank Center for East Asian Research, 1983-1986 (Box 77, f. 1)
    - Feldenkirken, Wilfried, 1984-1986 (Box 77, f. 2)
    - Feldman, Gerald D., 1984-1986 (Box 77, f. 3)
    - Fell, Thomas E., Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 77, f. 4)
    - Ferguson, Robert L., 1984 (Box 77, f. 5)
    - Ferguson, Thomas, 1983 (Box 77, f. 6)
    - Field, Alexander J., 1986 (Box 77, f. 7)
    - Firestone, undated (Box 77, f. 8)
    - Fischer, Wolfram, 1976-1977 (Box 77, f. 9)
    - Fitton, R.S., 1971 (Box 77, f. 10)
    - Flagler, Henry Morrison, 1987 (Box 77, f. 11)
    - Fleming, James, 1985 (Box 77, f. 12)
    - Fligstein, Neil, 1984 (Box 77, f. 13)
    - Flocks, Sally, 1976 (Box 77, f. 14)
    - Fogel, Robert W., 1971-1979 (Box 77, f. 15)
    - Fondazione, Giovanni Agnelli, 1973-1975 (Box 77, f. 16-17)
    - Fondazione, Giovanni Agnelli, 1973-1975 (Box 198, f. 1)
    - Forbes Magazine, 1987 (Box 77, f. 18)
    - Foulkes, Fred K., 1977 (Box 77, f. 19)
    - Fourie, Frederick, 1981-1982 (Box 77, f. 20)
    - Fox, Kenneth, 1975-1979 (Box 77, f. 21)
    - Fox, Ron, 1981-1984 (Box 77, f. 22)
    - Francis, Arthur, 1980-1981 (Box 77, f. 23)
    - Franko, Lawrence G., 1972-1984 (Box 77, f. 24)
    - Free Press, 1977-1985 (Box 77, f. 25)
    - Freeland, Richard M., 1978-1987 (Box 77, f. 26-31)
    - Freeze, Karen J., 1982 (Box 78, f. 1)
    - Frese, Joseph R., 1978-1980 (Box 78, f. 2)
    - Freudenberger, Herman (see also: Redlich Prize), 1978-1982 (Box 78, f. 3)
    - Freyer, Tony, 1974-1987 (Box 78, f. 4-6)
    - Fridenson, Patrick, 1974-1987 (Box 78, f. 7)
    - Fries, Russell and Sylvia, 1973-1985 (Box 78, f. 8)
    - Fruin, Mark, 1978-1985 (Box 78, f. 9-12)
    - G: Gabel-Ginswick, 1971-1987 (Box 78, f. 13)
    - G: Gitelman-Guttman, 1971-1987 (Box 78, f. 14)
    - Galambos, Louis, 1971-1987 (Box 78, f. 15-16)
    - Gale, Barbara, 1981 (Box 78, f. 17)
    - Gallman, Robert E., 1972-1976 (Box 78, f. 18)
    - Ganesh, S.R., 1983 (Box 78, f. 19)
    - Gebhard, Charles N., 1975 (Box 78, f. 20)
    - German Marshall/Sloan Project, 1978-1983 (Box 78, f. 21)
    - German Marshall Fellowship-Grant Application, 1977-1979 (Box 78, f. 22)
    - German Marshall Fellowship, 1977 (Box 78, f. 23)
    - Gesellschaft fur Unternehmensgeschichte, 1980-1981 (Box 79, f. 1)
    - Giebelhaus, Aug. 1976-1981 (Box 79, f. 2)
    - Gillet, J.P., 1980 (Box 79, f. 3)
    - Godine, David R., 1980-1983 (Box 79, f. 4)
    - Golden, Claudia, 1974-1984 (Box 79, f. 5)
    - Gomery, J. Douglas, 1975-1976 (Box 79, f. 6)
    - Goodpaster, Kenneth, 1982 (Box 79, f. 7)
    - Gospel, Howard, 1983-1986 (Box 79, f. 8)
    - Gourvish, Terry, 1973-1978 (Box 79, f. 9)
    - Grades, undated (Box 79, f. 10)
    - Graham, Margaret B.W., 1980 (Box 79, f. 11-12)
    - Grants (Australia/Canada), 1975-1976 (Box 79, f. 13)
    - Green, E.R.R., 1970-1971 (Box 79, f. 14)
    - Green, George, 1979-1981 (Box 79, f. 15)
    - Green, Rodney, 1970 (Box 79, f. 16)
    - Green, Thomas, 1972 (Box 79, f. 17)
    - Greenberg, Delores, 1975-1985 (Box 79, f. 18)
    - Greene, William N., 1979-1986 (Box 79, f. 19)
    - Greene, Suzanne, 1975-1977 (Box 79, f. 20)
    - Greenwich Research Associates, 1981 (Box 79, f. 21)
    - Greenwood Press, 1976-1986 (Box 79, f. 22)
    - Grego, Jaime, 1975-1978 (Box 79, f. 23)
    - Gregory, Frances, 1971-1980 (Box 79, f. 24)
    - Grey, Martin, 1984-1986 (Box 79, f. 25)
    - Gringer, Peter H., 1978-1981 (Box 79, f. 26)
    - Grundstein, Nathan D., 1981-1984 (Box 79, f. 27)
    - Guildhall Library, London, 1979 (Box 79, f. 28)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1972-1979 (Box 79, f. 29)
    - H: Haeberle-Hawthorne, 1972-1987 (Box 79, f. 30)
    - H: Hax-Hoffert, 1971-1987 (Box 79, f. 31)
    - H: Hogan-Hyman, 1971-1983 (Box 79, f. 32)
    - Hancock, Woodson, 1979 (Box 79, f. 33)
    - Hanieski, John, 1971-1972 (Box 79, f. 34)
    - Hannah, Leslie, 1973-1987 (Box 80, f. 1-4)
    - Hareven, Tamara K., 1979-1983 (Box 80, f. 5)
    - Harrell, Thomas W., 1976 (Box 80, f. 6)
    - Harris, John R., 1973-1976 (Box 80, f. 7)
    - Harris, William J., 1984 (Box 80, f. 8)
    - Harvard, John M., 1980 (Box 80, f. 9)
    - Harvard Business School (Articles), 1977-1980 (Box 80, f. 10)
    - Harvard University Press (Income), 1976-1985 (Box 80, f. 11)
    - Harvard University Press (Publications), 1976-1985 (Box 80, f. 12)
    - Hawley, Ellis W., 1979 (Box 80, f. 13)
    - Heilbroner, Robert L., 1978-1983 (Box 80, f. 14)
    - Heim, Carol, 1983-1986 (Box 80, f. 15)
    - Henri, Daniel, 1987 (Box 80, f. 16)
    - Herbst, Lawrence, 1977 (Box 80, f. 17)
    - Hewlett, Richard, 1979-1981 (Box 80, f. 18)
    - Hewes, James, 1971-1981 (Box 80, f. 19-21)
    - Hirshauer, Bruce, 1971-1978 (Box 80, f. 22)
    - Hodne, Fritz, 1983 (Box 81, f. 1)
    - Holt, Sarah, 1987 (Box 81, f. 2)
    - Home (Personal Matters), 1970-1972 (Box 81, f. 3)
    - Hoopes, Hames, 1971-1978 (Box 81, f. 4)
    - Hopper, Kenneth, 1985 (Box 81, f. 5)
    - Horwitch, Mel, 1976-1983 (Box 81, f. 6-7)
    - Hough, Gordon, 1976-1980 (Box 81, f. 8)
    - Hounshell, David, 1982 (Box 81, f. 9)
    - Howes, Leroy De Rosa, 1987 (Box 81, f. 10)
    - Hughes, Katherine, 1982-1985 (Box 81, f. 11)
    - Hughes, Thomas P., 1971-1984 (Box 81, f. 12-14)
    - Huillier, Daniel J., 1980 (Box 81, f. 15)
    - Hungerford, Arthur, 1984 (Box 81, f. 16)
    - Hutchinson, Martin, 1973-1979 (Box 81, f. 17)
    - Hwang, Myong Soo, 1983 (Box 81, f. 18)
    - I: Inglehart-Iwata, 1972-1987 (Box 81, f. 19)
    - Illinois, University of, 1973-1983 (Box 81, f. 20)
    - Industriens Utredningsinstitut, 1983 (Box 81, f. 21)
    - Ingham, John, 1978-1981 (Box 81, f. 22)
    - Inoue, Tadakatsu, 1971-1984 (Box 81, f. 23)
    - Institute of Management Sciences, The, 1979-1980 (Box 81, f. 24)
    - Institute Per La Ricostruzione, 1979 (Box 81, f. 25)
    - International Harvester, 1975-1976 (Box 81, f. 26)
    - Irwin, Richard D., Publishers, Inc., 1984-1987 (Box 81, f. 27)
    - Isdale, Joe W., 1981 (Box 81, f. 28)
    - J: Jacobs-Junkus, 1971-1987 (Box 81, f. 29)
    - Jacoby, Sanford M., 1978-1984 (Box 81, f. 30)
    - James, John, 1973-1983 (Box 82, f. 1)
    - Jacquemon, Alexis, 1976-1982 (Box 82, f. 2)
    - Japan- Yanagihara, Norio (Strategy and Structure), 1972-1978 (Box 82, f. 3)
    - Japanese Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 82, f. 4)
    - Japanese (Visiting) Scholars, 1975-1978 (Box 82, f. 5)
    - Jelinek, Mariann, 1976-1984 (Box 82, f. 6)
    - Jenkins, Reese V., 1975-1987 (Box 82, f. 7-8)
    - Johnson, Brett, 1984 (Box 82, f. 9)
    - Johnson, Robert, 1978-1982 (Box 82, f. 10)
    - Johnson, Roger T., 1971-1983 (Box 82, f. 11)
    - Johnson, Thomas, 1971-1987 (Box 82, f. 12-14)
    - Jones, Alice, 1983 (Box 82, f. 15)
    - Jones, Charles, 1982-1983 (Box 82, f. 16)
    - Jones, Edward A., undated (Box 82, f. 17)
    - Jones, Geoffrey, 1982-1987 (Box 82, f. 18)
    - Journal of American History, 1974-1986 (Box 82, f. 19)
    - Journal of Economic History, 1971-1979 (Box 82, f. 20)
    - K: Kagono-Kiger, 1972-1987 (Box 82, f. 21)
    - K: Kindleberger-Kusiatin, 1972-1987 (Box 82, f. 22)
    - Kaledin, Arthur, 1974 (Box 82, f. 23)
    - Kapstein, Ethan B., 1979-1981 (Box 82, f. 24)
    - Karamanski, Theodore, 1981 (Box 82, f. 25)
    - Karr, Ronald, 1981-1982 (Box 82, f. 25-27)
    - Kasper, Dan, 1976 (Box 82, f. 28)
    - Katusura, Yoshio, 1979 (Box 82, f. 29)
    - Kawabe, Nobuo, 1977-1982 (Box 82, f. 30)
    - Keller, Morton, 1977-1983 (Box 83, f. 1)
    - Kennedy, Charles J., 1972-1978 (Box 83, f. 2)